imscouting.com 2011-06-04

# IMScouting.com

Here at IMScouting.com, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy. Before submitting any information to the IMScouting Ltd., we encourage you to read the following Privacy Policy and learn how we will treat your personal information

By using any part of the IMScouting.com website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy and to the collection, processing and maintenance of this information in any applicable countries.

##### Collecting your Personal Information

During your visit to IMScouting.com, you will be asked to provide us with information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you (hereinafter: "Personal Information"). Generally, this information will be requested upon registering and creating your account or before posting to the forum. This Personal Information may vary but will typically include your first and last name, e-mail address, address (country, city) and phone number. You will also be requested to provide a unique member name and password to access and use certain features of the site. Also, in case you are purchasing a member package, a credit card number (including CID number) and expiration date may be required.

IMScouting Ltd. may also collect non-personally identifiable information, including traffic statistics regarding page views; other technical information, including users' Internet Protocol (IP) address and standard web log information; and supplemental information from third parties.

##### Use of your Personal Information

First, IMScouting Ltd. may use your Personal Information to provide you with services and information you have requested or content of member packages you have purchased. Second, IMScouting Ltd. may also use your Personal Information to respond to specific inquiries made by you, to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use; and to customize, measure, and improve our services, content and layout. Finally, IMScouting Ltd. may use your Personal Information to notify you about special offers, products, services, and information that we think may be of interest to you. You can opt-out of receiving commercial e-mail from us at any time.

IMScouting.com will disclose your Personal Information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on IMScouting Ltd. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of IMScouting Ltd., and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of IMScouting Ltd., its website, or the public.

##### Control of your Personal Information

From time to time, IMScouting Ltd. may share personally identifiable information with third parties we have engaged to perform certain services in connection with the operation of certain aspects of the IMScouting.com website, including customizing, measure and improving our services, content, and layout.

When you register, or otherwise give us Personal Information, IMScouting Ltd. will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

##### Security of your Personal Information

IMScouting Ltd. strictly protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under the conditions explained above. IMScouting Ltd. stores your Personal Information in password-controlled servers with limited access.

You also have a significant role in protecting your Personal Information. No one can see or edit your Personal Information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

##### Use of Cookies

IMScouting Ltd. uses "cookie" technology and users' IP addresses to customize and enhance your online experience on the site. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to your hard drive when you visit our site that automatically identify your browser to our server whenever you interact with our site. Such technology is a common feature of many web sites and is necessary in order for certain features of our site to function properly or in order to provide an online service to you (for instance, site registration). You may customize the browser settings of your computer to notify you when a browser cookie is sent or to refuse browser cookies altogether. Please check your browser for instructions on how to make these adjustments.

##### Changes to this Policy

IMScouting Ltd. will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of the Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Policy, those changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what personal information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information may be disclosed. Your continued use of IMScouting Ltd.'s website following the posting of changes to this Policy will signal your acceptance of such changes.

##### Contact

If you have any questions, comments, or requests regarding this Policy or the information practices of IMScouting Ltd., please contact us by e-mail at [info@imscouting.com](mailto:info@imscouting.com)

Last updated: April 2008.
